A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.14-SG 1.15 (A88-A89) FA478
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-2005; 1982-1988; 1.15; 42.49 Cubic Feet
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - Addis Ababa University - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A45), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 420)
    - Shanghai Medical University, Hua Shan Hospital - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A47), 1985, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 421)
    - Khon Kaen University - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A48), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 422)
      Dr. Kiertijai Bhuripunyo and Dr. Sumitr Sutra
    - Chulalongkorn University - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A49), 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 423)
      Dr. Ayut Dhamkrong-at
    - West China University of Medical Sciences - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A50), 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 424)
      Dr. Lei Bingjun
    - Escola Paulista de Medicina - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A51), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 425)
      Dr. Samuel Goihman, Dr. Alvaro Nagib Atallah, Dr. Ricardo de Castro Cintra Sesso
    - Mahidol University - Clinical Epidemiology (RF 85004 - HS) (A52), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 426)
      Dr. Nalinee Asawapokee and Dr. Nirun Vanprapar
    - Fourth Annual Meeting of the International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) (RF 85004) (A55), 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 427-432, Box 73, Folder 433-435)
      Folders 433-435 - Supplementary Material
    - Harvard University - Gossypol (RF 85011) (A36), 1982-1987 (Box 73, Folder 436-437, Box 74, Folder 438-439)
    - Lion Murard and Patrick Zylberman - "The Rockefeller Medicine Men in France (1917-1940): A Demonstration of Method" (RF 85013) (A380), 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 440)
    - Gilbert Martin - "Winston Churchill Biography, Volume 7" (RF 85013) (A381), 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 441)
    - Deirdre Bair - "Simone de Beauvoir: A Critical Biography" (RF 85013) (A382), 1984-1985, 1987, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 442)
    - Donald K. Swearer - "The Uses of Tradition: Contemporary Buddhist Social Ethics" (RF 85013) (A383), 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 443)
    - Allan M. Brandt - "The Social and Cultural History of Cigarette Smoking in American Life" (RF 85013) (A384), 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 444)
    - Allan F. Gibbard - "The Nature of Moral Judgment" (RF 85013) (A385), 1984-1987, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 445)
    - Steven E. G. Kemper - "Negotiating the Past: The Compilation of the Mahavamsa, The Sri Lankan National Chronicle" (RF 85013) (A386), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 446)
    - Linda O. McMurry - "The Talented Tenth in the New South, 1880-1920" (RF 85013) (A387), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 447)
    - Phyllis Mack - "Religious Culture and Gender in Early Modern England: Women and the Quaker Movement" (RF 85013) (A388), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 448)
    - Nancy K. Miller - "Reading Women's Writing: Female Authorship and the Novel in France" (RF 85013) (A389), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 449)
    - Karen Offen - "The Politics of Motherhood in France, 1920-1945" (RF 85013) (A390), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 450)
    - Margaret Susan Thompson - "The Yoke of Grace: American Nuns and Social Change, 1808-1917" (RF 85013) (A391), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 451)
    - Judith R. Walkowitz - "Gender and Violence in Metropolitan Culture: The Case of Late-Victorian London" (RF 85013) (A392), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 452)
    - Thomas Kessner - "Fiorello La Guardia and the Making of Modern New York" (RF 85013) (A393), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 453)
    - Judith Tick - "The Stratosphere and the Road: A Biography of Ruth Crawford Seeger (1901-1953)" (RF 85013) (A394), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 454)
    - Michael W. Harris - "The Emergence of Afro-American Gospel Blues as Seen Through the Life and Mind of Thomas Andrew Dorsey" (RF 85013) (A395), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 455)
    - Penelope D. Johnson - "Women and the Monastic Life in Medieval France" (RF 85013) (A396), 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 456)
    - Robert L. Herbert - "Seeing Impressionism: A Social Study of Themes of Leisure and Entertainment" (RF 85013) (A397), 1984-1988 (Box 75, Folder 457)
    - Evelyn Fox Keller - "The Language of Individualism in Evolutionary Discourse" (RF 85013) (A398), 1984-1987 (Box 76, Folder 458)
    - Judith Marcus - "The 'Budapest School' of Psychoanalysis: The History of a Movement (1910-1933)" (RF 85013) (A399), 1984-1987 (Box 76, Folder 459)
    - Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe, Inc. - Interdisciplinary Artists Program (A 85014) (A2), 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 460)
    - West Africa Rice Development Association - Staff Support (RF 85018), 1983-1989 (Box 76, Folder 461-464, Box 77, Folder 465-468)
    - National Humanities Center - Humanities Fellowships for Junior Scholars (RF 85025), 1984-1991, 1995, 1999-2001, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 469-470, Box 78, Folder 471)
    - L. Bartholomew Landry - "Mobility and Changing Opportunities Among Black Males" (RF 85032) (A107), 1985-1989 (Box 78, Folder 472)
    - Lillie Johnson Edwards - "From Alabama to Angola: A Biography of Henry Curtis McDowell - Afro-American Missionary" (RF 85032) (A108), 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 473)
    - Gail E. Thomas - "Participation and Success of Blacks in Graduate and Professional Education" (RF 85032) (A109), 1985-1988 (Box 78, Folder 474)
    - Huey L. Perry - "The Social and Economic Impact of Black Politics in the South" (RF 85032) (A110), 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 475)
    - Sharon Nelson-Le Gall - "Cognitive-Motivational Influences on Black Children's Academic Help Seeking" (RF 85032) (A111), 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 476)
    - Sonja Peterson-Lewis - "Why Women Return to Abusive Marital Relationships: An Analysis of Three Ethnic Minority Groups" (RF 85032) (A112), 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 477)
    - Thadious M. Davis - "Race and Reputation: A Comparative Study of Richard Wright and William Faulkner" (RF 85032) (A113), 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 478)
    - Editorial Projects in Education - Publication of "Education Week" (RF 85034), 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 479)
    - Learning in Focus, Inc. - Films for Television (RF 85038), 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 480-483, Box 80, Folder 484-485)
      Folders 484-485 - Supplementary Material
      - Learning in Focus, "Seize the Day", Reel 1 of 2, 4/3/86, 2017:FA478:007 (Box 80, Folder 485)
        Videotape
      - Learning in Focus, "Seize the Day", Reel 2 of 2, 4/3/86, 2017:FA478:008 (Box 80, Folder 485)
    - National Arts Stabilization Fund, Inc. (RF 85040), 1982-1989, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 486-488, Box 81, Folder 489-492)
    - Yu Yong Xin - Research Project on Japanese Encephalitis Vaccine (RF 85042) (A3), 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 493)
    - Mahidol University - Neurosafety Primate Testing Facility (RF 85042) (A4), 1985-1988 (Box 82, Folder 494)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Family Planning Program in the Developing World (RF 85045), 1984-1989, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 495-498, Box 83, Folder 499-503, Box 84, Folder 504-508, Box 85, Folder 509-510)
      Folders 505-510 - Supplementary Material
    - Clark College - Southern Center for Studies in Public Policy (RF 85052), 1973-1987, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 511-513, Box 86, Folder 514-519, Box 87, Folder 520-523, Box 88, Box 524-528, Box 89, Folder 529-532, Box 90, Folder 533-536, Box 91, Folder 537-539)
      Folders 518-539 - Supplementary Material
    - National Urban League - Permanent Development Fund (RF 85069), 1984-1989, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 540-542, Box 92, Folder 543)
    - Tufts University - Division of Geographic Medicine (RF 85078) (A115), 1977-1987 (Box 92, Folder 544-547)
    - Urban Affairs Partnership - Philadelphia Alliance for Teaching Humanities in the Schools (PATHS) (RF 85088), 1983-1987, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 548-553, Box 94, Folder 554-559, Box 95, Folder 560-562)
      - Philadelphia Alliance for Teaching Humanities in the Schools (PATHS) - Mini Grants Video - 12/5/85, 2017:FA478:009 (Box 95, Folder 560)
        Videocassette
      - Urban Affairs Partnership - Philadelphia Schools and Humanities, 2017:FA478:010 (Box 95, Folder 560)
        Audiocassette
      - Urban Affairs Partnership - Philadelphia Schools and Humanities, 2017:FA478:011 (Box 95, Folder 560)
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute - Research Program on Adolescent Pregnancy (RF 86021), 1978-1988 (Box 95, Folder 563-564, Box 96, Folder 565-567, Box 97, Folder 568-573)